[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a type of chipmunk?", "correct_answer": "Bushy-tailed", "incorrect_answers": ["Long-eared", "Eastern", "Sonoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mucus is a slippery secretion of the lining of various membranes typical for which system of the human body?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Reproductive system", "Digestive system", "Respiratory system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phrase means I love you in Russian?", "correct_answer": "Ya lyublyu tebya", "incorrect_answers": ["Eu te amo", "Te iu besc", "Volim te"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Burkes first name in the movie Aliens?", "correct_answer": "Carter", "incorrect_answers": ["Chuck", "Clarence", "Charles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Top Dollars right hand man in The Crow?", "correct_answer": "Grange", "incorrect_answers": ["Shades", "Markus", "Lau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pangolins have no teeth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. President is famous for saying I choose not to run?", "correct_answer": "Calvin Coolidge", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbert Hoover", "John Tyler", "Warren G. Harding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress who was in Clueless was also in the movie Look Whos Talking?", "correct_answer": "Twink Caplan", "incorrect_answers": ["Brittany Murphy", "Stacy Dash", "Elisa Donovan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Parrot fish, found in the Atlantic Indian and Pacific Ocean reefs, was given its name for what reason?", "correct_answer": "Because of its beak-like mouth", "incorrect_answers": ["Because of the shape of its body", "Because it can fly a few metres above water", "Because its body is in different flashy colours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At least twice an actor/actress has been nominated for a Razzie and an Oscar for the same performance. Who was the first actress to achieve this distinction?", "correct_answer": "Amy Irving", "incorrect_answers": ["LIza Minelli", "Judy Garland", "Barbra Streisand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious is a word used in this film.", "correct_answer": "Mary Poppins", "incorrect_answers": ["Flubber", "Peter Pan", "Sound of Music"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which American state means red people in the Choctaw language?", "correct_answer": "Oklahoma", "incorrect_answers": ["Ohio", "North Dakota", "Oregon"]}]